

PROFESSIONAL

Full-stack development Layout design Scrum Angular C# Source control management

Issue management systems

PERSONAL

(Jira, Azure)

Creative spirit Reliable and professional Time management Problem-solving Team player Collaborating with other developers Fast learner Motivated

CONTACT

My site:

https://www.kismarczi.hu/my-site/

+36 30 207 5454

kismarczirobi@gmail.com



Github

in Linkedin

Hungary, szeged

JOZSEF KISMARCZI

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

My name is József Kismarczi and I have been involved in active development since 2018. My skills include the implementation of web design and development principles to create reliable software both on the backend and front-end. I bring mockups to life using a variety of tools, such as HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript (ES6), TypeScript, jQuery and Angular. I am able to communicate technical issues clearly and comprehensibly to the development team. I create responsive and user-friendly products and applications, then monitor their performance and solve problems. I use version control tools like Git to maintain an organized workflow. I have experience in using the .net framework. On the back-end, I also try to comply with SOLID principles, clean code rules and using design patterns to create a WEB API with better performance and more transparent code.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Signal Iduna | 2022 - Now

• Stacks: C#, Angular

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

NewLine kft. | 2019 - 2022

- Developing public trasport schedule system websites
- Stacks: C#, Kendo UI, MVC, TypeScript, GIT/TFS, SQL, Web API

FRONT END SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Pc Trade Systems kft. | Jun 2018 - Dec 2018

• Angular, Scrum, Jira ticket management

EDUCATION

FLOW ACADEMY - Software developer | 2018